packagingoftheworld.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy | Packaging of the World Submissions

Your privacy is very important to us. At Packaging of the World we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.  
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.  
Packaging of the World operates several websites including PackagingoftheWorld.com. It is Packaging of the World’ policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Packaging of the World collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Packaging of the World’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Packaging of the World’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Packaging of the World may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Packaging of the World also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. Packaging of the World only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Submission Form**

By uploading your project(s) or content to this Packaging of the World (POTW), you agree to these terms and conditions and POTW’s Web Site User Agreement, Privacy Policy, and Acceptable Use Policy, which are incorporated herein by reference. If you do not agree, you should not upload to this Site. By submitting your image, graphic, video, artwork , logo, trademark or other content (“Content”) to this Web Site, you represent that You have the full rights to upload your Content and that uploading your Content to this Site will not violate or infringe the rights of any third person, including but not limited to, rights in copyrights, patents, trademarks, trade secrets or other proprietary rights. You further represent that you will not upload any Content that is defamatory, obscene, in violation of any law, or contains any viruses, “worms”, “trojan horses” or any other harmful or destructive properties. You grant to POTW, a perpetual, royalty-free, non-exclusive, worldwide license to electronically publish and distribute the Content in all versions of the Site including the right to translate and electronically publish and distribute the Content to other Internet Sites under license, contract or common ownership with the POTW. Finally, we reserve the right to refuse the uploading or listing of your Content or to remove and/or delete your Content at any time, for any reason. The Site is provided “as is” without warranties of any kind. The Site and POTW expressly disclaim all warranties, express or implied, including, without limitation, the warranties of merchantability or fitness of purpose. You hereby release the Site and POTW from any and all costs, expenses, claims or liabilities that are in any way related to your use of the Site, or your uploading of the Content. You agree to fully defend and indemnify the Site and POTW from, and against, any and all costs, expenses, claims or liabilities incurred by the Site or POTW as a result Content that you have uploaded or your breach of any of these terms and conditions.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Packaging of the World’s websites choose to interact with Packaging of the World in ways that require Packaging of the World to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Packaging of the World gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive Packaging of the World updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, Packaging of the World collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Packaging of the World. Packaging of the World does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Packaging of the World may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Packaging of the World may monitor the most popular pages on the PackagingoftheWorld.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. Packaging of the World may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Packaging of the World does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Packaging of the World discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Packaging of the World’ behalf or to provide services available at Packaging of the World’ websites, and (ii) have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Packaging of the World’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Packaging of the World will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Packaging of the World discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Packaging of the World believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Packaging of the World, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Packaging of the World website and have supplied your email address, Packaging of the World may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Packaging of the World and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Packaging of the World takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Packaging of the World uses cookies to help Packaging of the World identify and track visitors, their usage of the Packaging of the World website, and their website access preferences. Packaging of the World visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Packaging of the World’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of Packaging of the World’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If Packaging of the World, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Packaging of the World goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Packaging of the World may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Packaging of the World and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Comments**

Comments and other content submitted to blogger commenting system are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Packaging of the World may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Packaging of the World’ sole discretion. Packaging of the World encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
